

## **Profile**

I'm a dedicated Full stack software developer, specializing mostly in C#, ASP.NET, Javascript, Angular, MySQL Databases, and I also write PHP / Laravel code. Currently, I'm on final year on ICT College, Belgrade. For the past 3.5 years I'm actively learning programming. I'm a hardworking person, and I can work in team since I have 4 years of working experience outside of programming, and 5 months experience in programming field.

Currently I'm actively reading programming books such as "Head first design patterns" and "Clean Code" so that i keep improving my knowledge in software engineering and development.

# **Employment History**

Laravel Backend Developer, IT Development Solutions, Pančevo

APRIL 2022 - JUNE 2022

- · Worked to meet client deadlines.
- Effetively multitasked and worked well with internal and external teams.
- Worked to assess competing websites in regards to content, database design, and performance.
- Effectively translated client requirements into application designs and system requirements.

#### Software Developer, Quadro Consulting, Belgrade

JUNE 2022 - PRESENT

- Effectively coded software changes and alterations based on specific design specifications.
- Worked with various design patterns such as Builder, CQRS (Command Query Responsibility Segregation), SOLID principles etc.
- Helped to provide industry-leading solutions.
- Utilized the latest software development tools, techniques, and approaches.

## Education

ICT College, Belgrade

OCTOBER 2019 - DECEMBER 2022

Department for Internet Technologies - Web Programming, software engineering

#### Courses

C# Intermediate, Udemy

Javascript Intermediate, Udemy

#### **Details**

Pančevo Serbia +381/65-368-3833

lazicn378@gmail.com

## Links

Linkedin

**GitHub** 

### **Backend skills**

HTML5

JavaScript

Angular

Bootstrap 4,5

Sass

PHP

Laravel Framework

C# .NET

ASP.NET

ASP.NET Core

ASP.NET MVC

**Entity Framework** 

**SQL** Server

SQL

## Languages

Serbian

English